In the Marvelous Designer software, enter a shop that can buy clothing items.
On the far left of the screen, there are the General, Basic and Store shop labels.
Select Store to open the shop.
If you need to log in, please enter the user account and password on the Marvelous Designer official website at the window in the pop-up window.
Enter your business account and your personal account.
Select the mouse to check the name and price on the object.
For your favorite products, you can click the Like icon.
You can enter keywords or use the filter to check the required categories.
You can use the pull-down menu on the top right to sort the products.
If you don't want to browse the products you have purchased, please open the display to have the product.
If you want to double-click on the product, you can find the detailed information of the product under the details tab on the right side.
You can see the seller's name at the bottom of the product name.
You can choose the purchase type of license.
You can see the purchase type of license at the bottom of the product name.
Click the 3D Viewer button to view the product in the 3D environment.
You can adjust the rendering style of the product according to your needs.
You can also click the basic information and product description in the detail tab.
You can view the product pictures uploaded by the seller.
Click the arrow button on both sides of the picture or select the page number at the bottom to view other pictures.
Click the arrow button on both sides of the picture or select the page number at the bottom of the picture.
Let's take a look at the grapes and figs in this clip.
Click the icon on the right of the video to watch the review.
There are several activities for buying.
Click the Amazon problems tab on the upper left to view the changes.
Click and close to see the conveyor belt option you just made in three units in this clip.
Once you have this, please see the selected products and clear.
Click again onências to read through and prepare for the next step.
Click Next.
Enter your purchase information and complete your purchase.
Purchased products can be downloaded to my page under the product page.
When the purchase is completed, return to the general basic page and enter the purchased product, which can be used in Marvelous Designer.